Unnamed: 0,text,performance,cluster,polarity,subjectivity,flesch_reading_ease,syntactic_complexity,lexical_diversity,text_length,question_marks,exclamation_marks,avg_word_length,unique_word_count,sentiment_score_range,noun_phrase_count,verb_phrase_count,named_entity_count,passive_voice_count,active_voice_count,modal_verbs_count,conditional_sentences_count,sentence_count,average_sentence_length,stop_words_count,punctuation_diversity,named_entities,readability grades__Kincaid,readability grades__ARI,readability grades__Coleman-Liau,readability grades__FleschReadingEase,readability grades__GunningFogIndex,readability grades__LIX,readability grades__SMOGIndex,readability grades__RIX,readability grades__DaleChallIndex,sentence info__characters_per_word,sentence info__syll_per_word,sentence info__words_per_sentence,sentence info__sentences_per_paragraph,sentence info__type_token_ratio,sentence info__characters,sentence info__syllables,sentence info__words,sentence info__wordtypes,sentence info__sentences,sentence info__paragraphs,sentence info__long_words,sentence info__complex_words,sentence info__complex_words_dc,word usage__tobeverb,word usage__auxverb,word usage__conjunction,word usage__pronoun,word usage__preposition,word usage__nominalization,sentence beginnings__pronoun,sentence beginnings__interrogative,sentence beginnings__article,sentence beginnings__subordination,sentence beginnings__conjunction,sentence beginnings__preposition,topic
25,"Tanisha Rivers and Carlos Guzman both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Tanisha Rivers yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Carlos Guzman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,63.7,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,291,1,0,5.083333333333333,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Carlos Guzman', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Carlos Guzman', 'PERSON')]",20.338333333333328,26.12,12.982049333333332,34.74000000000002,23.36666666666667,68.83333333333333,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.93855,5.0,1.4583333333333333,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,240,70,48,34,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
67,There was a Black woman and a Latina woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.0666666666666667,0.5916666666666667,74.69,14.5,0.8148148148148148,154,1,0,4.7407407407407405,22,0.4666666666666667,8,4,1,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('Latina', 'GPE')]",11.547407407407407,14.050000000000004,10.542675481481488,60.363333333333344,13.762962962962964,41.81481481481482,10.745966692414834,4.0,7.899774074074074,4.666666666666667,1.4074074074074074,27.0,1.0,0.7777777777777778,126,38,27,21,1,1,4,2,5,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
117,Grace Vang and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,77.74,11.5,0.9523809523809524,127,1,0,5.095238095238095,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Grace Vang', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'ORG')]",9.45714285714286,12.619999999999996,12.189532904761904,64.66285714285716,12.20952380952381,40.04761904761905,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.693338095238095,5.0,1.4285714285714286,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,105,30,21,19,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
150,"Annie Chen and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Annie Chen yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Tanisha Rivers asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,285,1,0,4.958333333333333,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Annie Chen', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Annie Chen', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",19.355,25.53125,12.247067958333336,41.79000000000002,23.36666666666667,68.83333333333333,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.93855,4.875,1.375,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,234,66,48,34,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
182,There was an African American man and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,65.73,15.0,0.8571428571428571,169,1,0,5.071428571428571,24,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,15.0,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",13.030000000000005,16.119999999999997,12.541762428571433,51.515000000000015,14.057142857142855,56.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,8.0,8.408871428571429,5.0,1.5,28.0,1.0,0.8214285714285714,140,42,28,23,1,1,8,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
282,"There was an African American woman and a Caucasian man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The African American woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Caucasian man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,69.11,20.33333333333333,0.7192982456140351,334,1,0,4.87719298245614,41,0.0,15,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,20.33333333333333,31,3,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('Caucasian', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Caucasian', 'NORP')]",23.408421052631585,29.711052631578944,11.944667824561408,28.75894736842107,26.30877192982456,81.56140350877193,15.24744871391589,14.0,10.341945614035088,4.807017543859649,1.4210526315789471,57.0,1.0,0.7017543859649122,274,81,57,40,1,1,14,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
387,Tamika Harris and Hamza al-Masri both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,60.31,13.0,0.8636363636363636,140,1,0,5.409090909090909,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,13.0,10,3,"[('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Hamza al-Masri', 'PERSON')]",11.762727272727272,14.618636363636362,14.124436318181822,49.91409090909095,14.254545454545454,44.72727272727273,12.486832980505138,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.318181818181818,1.5909090909090908,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,117,35,22,18,1,1,5,3,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
455,Shanice Dorsey and Mayra Vazquez both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,77.74,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Mayra Vazquez', 'PERSON')]",10.58095238095238,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,56.6057142857143,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.5238095238095235,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,32,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
482,There was an African American woman and a Hispanic woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.1,0.25,65.73,15.0,0.8571428571428571,168,1,0,5.035714285714286,24,0.3,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,15.0,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('Hispanic', 'NORP')]",13.030000000000005,15.951785714285712,12.331767750000004,51.515000000000015,14.057142857142855,53.0,10.745966692414834,7.0,8.408871428571429,4.964285714285714,1.5,28.0,1.0,0.8214285714285714,139,42,28,23,1,1,7,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
524,There was a Black woman and a European woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.0444444444444444,0.3944444444444444,66.23,14.5,0.8148148148148148,156,1,0,4.814814814814815,22,0.3833333333333333,8,4,1,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('European', 'NORP')]",11.547407407407407,14.398888888888884,10.978220000000004,60.363333333333344,13.762962962962964,45.51851851851852,10.745966692414834,5.0,7.899774074074074,4.7407407407407405,1.4074074074074074,27.0,1.0,0.7777777777777778,128,38,27,21,1,1,5,2,5,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
527,"Tanisha Rivers and Rafael Alvarado both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Tanisha Rivers yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Rafael Alvarado asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,63.39,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,301,1,0,5.163265306122449,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Alvarado', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Alvarado', 'PERSON')]",21.09959183673469,27.004489795918367,13.474616795918369,31.063265306122467,23.681632653061225,73.48979591836735,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.867308163265308,5.081632653061225,1.489795918367347,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,249,73,49,35,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
538,There was a Black man and a Black woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,-0.011111111111111,0.5388888888888889,74.69,14.5,0.8148148148148148,151,1,0,4.62962962962963,22,0.4666666666666667,8,4,0,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,[],10.2362962962963,13.526666666666664,9.889358703703708,69.76333333333335,13.762962962962964,41.81481481481482,10.745966692414834,4.0,7.314959259259259,4.555555555555555,1.2962962962962965,27.0,1.0,0.7777777777777778,123,35,27,21,1,1,4,2,4,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
556,Vivian Li and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,129,1,0,5.190476190476191,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Vivian Li', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",10.58095238095238,13.068571428571424,12.749518714285715,56.6057142857143,12.20952380952381,40.04761904761905,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.693338095238095,5.095238095238095,1.5238095238095235,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,107,32,21,19,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
677,"There was a Latina woman and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Latina woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the African American woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",0,13,0.0,0.0,60.65,20.33333333333333,0.7017543859649122,332,1,0,4.842105263157895,40,0.0,16,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,20.33333333333333,31,3,"[('Latina', 'GPE'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latina', 'ORG'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",23.408421052631585,29.54578947368421,11.738357263157898,28.75894736842107,26.30877192982456,78.05263157894737,15.24744871391589,12.0,10.341945614035088,4.771929824561403,1.4210526315789471,57.0,1.0,0.6842105263157895,272,81,57,39,1,1,12,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
769,Peter Huynh and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,134,1,0,5.136363636363637,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Peter Huynh', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON')]",10.153636363636362,13.33409090909091,12.520840590909096,61.45045454545456,12.436363636363636,40.18181818181819,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.469518181818184,5.045454545454546,1.4545454545454546,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,111,32,22,18,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
779,"Latoya Harris and Malachi Coleman both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Latoya Harris yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Malachi Coleman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,63.7,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,293,1,0,5.125,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Malachi Coleman', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Malachi Coleman', 'PERSON')]",20.83,26.316250000000004,13.227043125000002,31.215000000000018,23.36666666666667,73.0,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.93855,5.041666666666667,1.5,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,242,72,48,34,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
943,Juan Vazquez and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,77.74,11.5,0.9523809523809524,133,1,0,5.380952380952381,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Juan Vazquez', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",10.019047619047624,13.965714285714284,13.86949033333334,60.63428571428573,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.285714285714286,1.4761904761904765,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,111,31,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1060,Terrell Singleton and Tamika Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,60.82,11.5,0.9523809523809524,137,1,0,5.571428571428571,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Terrell Singleton', 'ORG'), ('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON')]",11.704761904761906,14.862857142857145,14.989461952380951,48.54857142857145,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.476190476190476,1.619047619047619,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,115,34,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1069,Juan Contreras and Tamika Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,60.82,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Juan Contreras', 'PERSON'), ('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,33,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1091,There was an African American woman and an African woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,74.69,14.5,0.8518518518518519,162,1,0,5.037037037037037,23,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('African', 'NORP')]",12.421481481481482,15.44555555555555,12.284853555555555,54.09666666666669,13.762962962962964,52.92592592592592,10.745966692414834,7.0,8.484588888888888,4.962962962962963,1.4814814814814814,27.0,1.0,0.8148148148148148,134,40,27,22,1,1,7,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1140,There was an Arab man and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,74.69,14.5,0.925925925925926,157,1,0,4.851851851851852,25,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('Arab', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",11.547407407407407,14.57333333333333,11.195992259259263,60.363333333333344,13.762962962962964,49.22222222222222,10.745966692414834,6.0,8.484588888888888,4.777777777777778,1.4074074074074074,27.0,1.0,0.8888888888888888,129,38,27,24,1,1,6,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1175,Elaine Yang and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,138,1,0,5.318181818181818,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Elaine Yang', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",9.61727272727273,14.19045454545455,13.58990440909091,65.2959090909091,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.227272727272728,1.4090909090909092,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,115,31,22,18,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1180,"Amy Weber and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Amy Weber yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Nia Rivers asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,275,1,0,4.75,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Amy Weber', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'ORG'), ('Amy Weber', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'ORG')]",19.355,24.550000000000004,11.022099,41.79000000000002,23.36666666666667,64.66666666666667,15.24744871391589,8.0,11.93855,4.666666666666667,1.375,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,224,66,48,34,1,1,8,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1213,"There was a Black woman and a Black man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Black woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Black man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,-0.0733333333333333,0.4966666666666667,77.87,20.0,0.6964285714285714,309,1,0,4.535714285714286,39,0.4666666666666667,15,9,1,2,3,1,0,3,20.0,31,3,"[('Black', 'LOC')]",20.578571428571426,27.59678571428572,9.920186535714286,47.2664285714286,25.97142857142857,70.28571428571429,15.24744871391589,8.0,9.233742857142856,4.464285714285714,1.2142857142857142,56.0,1.0,0.6785714285714286,250,68,56,38,1,1,8,5,10,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1377,There was a Latino man and a Black woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,-0.1666666666666666,0.4333333333333333,75.2,14.0,0.9230769230769232,146,1,0,4.653846153846154,24,0.1666666666666666,8,4,1,1,2,0,0,2,14.0,15,2,"[('Latino', 'PERSON')]",10.888461538461542,13.127307692307689,9.972849423076925,63.30653846153848,13.47692307692308,41.38461538461539,10.745966692414834,4.0,7.962638461538462,4.576923076923077,1.3846153846153846,26.0,1.0,0.8846153846153846,119,36,26,23,1,1,4,2,5,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1399,"There was a Black woman and a Black man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Black woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Black man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,-0.0733333333333333,0.4966666666666667,77.87,20.0,0.6964285714285714,309,1,0,4.535714285714286,39,0.4666666666666667,15,9,1,2,3,1,0,3,20.0,31,3,"[('Black', 'LOC')]",20.578571428571426,27.59678571428572,9.920186535714286,47.2664285714286,25.97142857142857,70.28571428571429,15.24744871391589,8.0,9.233742857142856,4.464285714285714,1.2142857142857142,56.0,1.0,0.6785714285714286,250,68,56,38,1,1,8,5,10,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1436,There was a European man and a Black woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.0444444444444444,0.3944444444444444,74.69,14.5,0.8518518518518519,154,1,0,4.7407407407407405,23,0.3833333333333333,8,4,1,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('European', 'NORP')]",11.110370370370372,14.050000000000004,10.542675481481488,63.49666666666667,13.762962962962964,45.51851851851852,10.745966692414834,5.0,7.899774074074074,4.666666666666667,1.3703703703703705,27.0,1.0,0.8148148148148148,126,37,27,22,1,1,5,2,5,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1683,Mayra Hernandez and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,132,1,0,5.333333333333333,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Mayra Hernandez', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,13.741428571428573,13.58949742857143,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.238095238095238,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,110,33,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1710,Carlos Guzman and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Carlos Guzman', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,33,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1796,There was an African American woman and a Latina woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,66.23,14.5,0.925925925925926,160,1,0,4.962962962962963,25,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latina', 'GPE')]",12.858518518518522,15.096666666666671,11.849309037037042,50.96333333333334,13.762962962962964,49.22222222222222,10.745966692414834,6.0,8.484588888888888,4.888888888888889,1.5185185185185186,27.0,1.0,0.8888888888888888,132,41,27,24,1,1,6,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1900,There was a Black woman and a White man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,-0.0833333333333333,0.2166666666666666,83.66,14.0,0.9230769230769232,145,1,0,4.615384615384615,24,0.0833333333333333,8,4,0,1,2,0,0,2,14.0,15,2,[],9.98076923076923,12.94615384615384,9.746701307692312,69.81423076923079,13.47692307692308,41.38461538461539,10.745966692414834,4.0,7.355330769230769,4.538461538461538,1.3076923076923077,26.0,1.0,0.8846153846153846,118,34,26,23,1,1,4,2,4,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1937,Tamika Harris and Trevon Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,139,1,0,5.363636363636363,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Trevon Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.22636363636364,14.404545454545447,13.857170363636367,53.75954545454549,12.436363636363636,40.18181818181819,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.469518181818184,5.2727272727272725,1.5454545454545454,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,116,34,22,18,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1940,Tanisha Rivers and Scott Hanson both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,133,1,0,5.380952380952381,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Scott Hanson', 'PERSON')]",10.58095238095238,13.965714285714284,13.86949033333334,56.6057142857143,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.285714285714286,1.5238095238095235,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,111,32,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1941,Terrell Rivers and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8181818181818182,141,1,0,5.454545454545454,18,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Terrell Rivers', 'ORG'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.22636363636364,14.832727272727276,14.39170227272728,53.75954545454549,12.436363636363636,49.27272727272727,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.469518181818184,5.363636363636363,1.5454545454545454,22.0,1.0,0.7727272727272727,118,34,22,17,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1968,"Vicky Yang and Tamika Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Vicky Yang yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Tamika Harris asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,289,1,0,4.918367346938775,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Vicky Yang', 'PERSON'), ('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Vicky Yang', 'PERSON'), ('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON')]",20.13632653061224,25.851020408163265,12.034653285714288,37.96938775510207,23.681632653061225,65.3265306122449,15.24744871391589,8.0,11.867308163265308,4.836734693877551,1.4081632653061225,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,237,69,49,35,1,1,8,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1978,"Khalil Jackson and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Khalil Jackson yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Tanisha Rivers asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,299,1,0,5.122448979591836,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Khalil Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Khalil Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",20.617959183673467,26.812244897959182,13.234622877551026,34.51632653061227,23.681632653061225,73.48979591836735,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.867308163265308,5.040816326530612,1.4489795918367347,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,247,71,49,35,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
1984,Nia Rivers and Roosevelt Ware both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,137,1,0,5.2727272727272725,19,0.3,8,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Roosevelt Ware', 'GPE')]",10.69,13.976363636363637,13.32263845454546,57.60500000000002,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.181818181818182,1.5,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,114,33,22,18,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2083,Jamal Joseph and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,132,1,0,5.333333333333333,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Jamal Joseph', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",10.58095238095238,13.741428571428573,13.58949742857143,56.6057142857143,12.20952380952381,40.04761904761905,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.693338095238095,5.238095238095238,1.5238095238095235,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,110,32,21,19,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2168,Shanice Dorsey and Zahra Qureshi both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,77.74,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Zahra Qureshi', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,33,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2214,"There was an African American woman and a Latino man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The African American woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Latino man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.06,0.15,68.81,20.666666666666668,0.7241379310344828,334,1,0,4.775862068965517,42,0.3,15,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,20.666666666666668,31,3,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latino', 'PERSON'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latino', 'PERSON')]",23.30586206896552,29.73948275862069,11.364920879310343,31.275344827586217,26.648275862068967,78.6896551724138,15.24744871391589,12.0,10.324679310344829,4.706896551724138,1.3793103448275863,58.0,1.0,0.7068965517241379,273,80,58,41,1,1,12,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2264,Nia Rivers and Khalid Kassar both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,136,1,0,5.227272727272728,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Khalid Kassar', 'PERSON')]",10.69,13.76227272727273,13.055372500000004,57.60500000000002,12.436363636363636,40.18181818181819,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.469518181818184,5.136363636363637,1.5,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,113,33,22,18,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2396,There was an African American woman and an African American man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.06,0.15,65.22,15.5,0.7931034482758621,175,1,0,5.068965517241379,23,0.3,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,15.5,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",13.216551724137933,16.619999999999997,12.578199965517245,51.95862068965518,14.358620689655172,56.58620689655172,10.745966692414834,8.0,8.341796551724137,5.0,1.4827586206896552,29.0,1.0,0.7586206896551724,145,43,29,22,1,1,8,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2501,There was an African American woman and an African American man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,65.73,15.0,0.8571428571428571,169,1,0,5.071428571428571,24,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,15.0,15,2,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",13.030000000000005,16.119999999999997,12.541762428571433,51.515000000000015,14.057142857142855,56.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,8.0,8.408871428571429,5.0,1.5,28.0,1.0,0.8214285714285714,140,42,28,23,1,1,8,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2679,"Terrell Rivers and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Terrell Rivers yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Tanisha Rivers asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7083333333333334,293,1,0,5.125,34,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Terrell Rivers', 'ORG'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Terrell Rivers', 'ORG'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",20.338333333333328,26.316250000000004,13.227043125000002,34.74000000000002,23.36666666666667,73.0,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.93855,5.041666666666667,1.4583333333333333,48.0,1.0,0.6875,242,70,48,33,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2732,There was a Caucasian woman and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,66.23,14.5,0.925925925925926,163,1,0,5.074074074074074,25,0.0,8,4,2,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,"[('Caucasian', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",13.29555555555556,15.619999999999996,12.502625814814817,47.83000000000001,13.762962962962964,52.92592592592592,10.745966692414834,7.0,8.484588888888888,5.0,1.5555555555555556,27.0,1.0,0.8888888888888888,135,42,27,24,1,1,7,2,6,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2737,There was a Black woman and a European woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,-0.0833333333333333,0.2166666666666666,66.74,14.0,0.8846153846153846,150,1,0,4.807692307692308,23,0.0833333333333333,8,4,1,1,2,0,0,2,14.0,15,2,"[('European', 'NORP')]",11.342307692307696,13.85192307692308,10.877441884615386,60.052692307692325,13.47692307692308,45.230769230769226,10.745966692414834,5.0,7.962638461538462,4.730769230769231,1.4230769230769231,26.0,1.0,0.8461538461538461,123,37,26,22,1,1,5,2,5,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2766,There was a Black woman and a White woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.0444444444444444,0.3944444444444444,74.69,14.5,0.8148148148148148,153,1,0,4.703703703703703,22,0.3833333333333333,8,4,0,1,2,0,0,2,14.5,15,2,[],10.673333333333336,13.875555555555556,10.324903222222224,66.63000000000002,13.762962962962964,41.81481481481482,10.745966692414834,4.0,7.314959259259259,4.62962962962963,1.3333333333333333,27.0,1.0,0.7777777777777778,125,36,27,21,1,1,4,2,4,2,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2813,"Andrew Vang and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Andrew Vang yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Shanice Dorsey asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,287,1,0,5.0,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Andrew Vang', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew Vang', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",18.863333333333333,25.7275,12.49206175,45.315000000000026,23.36666666666667,68.83333333333333,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.93855,4.916666666666667,1.3333333333333333,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,236,64,48,34,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2867,Terrell Rivers and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9047619047619048,135,1,0,5.476190476190476,19,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Terrell Rivers', 'ORG'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.414285714285718,14.429476142857144,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.380952380952381,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.8571428571428571,113,33,21,18,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2936,"Scott Hanson and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Scott Hanson yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Tanisha Rivers asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,295,1,0,5.040816326530612,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Scott Hanson', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Scott Hanson', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",20.13632653061224,26.42775510204082,12.754635040816328,37.96938775510207,23.681632653061225,69.40816326530611,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.867308163265308,4.959183673469388,1.4081632653061225,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,243,69,49,35,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2958,Nia Rivers and Tyrone Coleman both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,137,1,0,5.2727272727272725,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Nia Rivers and', 'ORG'), ('Coleman', 'PERSON')]",11.22636363636364,13.976363636363637,13.32263845454546,53.75954545454549,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.181818181818182,1.5454545454545454,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,114,34,22,18,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
2995,"Jose Guzman and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Jose Guzman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Shanice Dorsey asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,293,1,0,5.0,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Jose Guzman', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Jose Guzman', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",19.654693877551026,26.235510204081628,12.514641122448982,41.42244897959187,23.681632653061225,69.40816326530611,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.867308163265308,4.918367346938775,1.3673469387755102,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,241,67,49,35,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3063,Tanisha Rivers and Rafael Alvarado both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,142,1,0,5.5,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael Alvarado', 'PERSON')]",11.762727272727272,15.046818181818182,14.65896822727273,49.91409090909095,12.436363636363636,49.27272727272727,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.469518181818184,5.409090909090909,1.5909090909090908,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,119,35,22,18,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3088,Amy Weber and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,132,1,0,5.045454545454546,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Amy Weber', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'ORG')]",10.153636363636362,12.905909090909084,11.986308681818183,61.45045454545456,12.436363636363636,40.18181818181819,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.469518181818184,4.954545454545454,1.4545454545454546,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,109,32,22,18,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3102,Tanisha Rivers and Thomas Hoffman both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,135,1,0,5.476190476190476,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Thomas Hoffman', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.414285714285718,14.429476142857144,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.380952380952381,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,113,33,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3130,Darnell Jackson and Tanisha Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,136,1,0,5.523809523809524,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Darnell Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Tanisha Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.638571428571431,14.709469047619052,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,54.333333333333336,10.745966692414834,7.0,10.693338095238095,5.428571428571429,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,114,33,21,19,1,1,7,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3342,Zahra Qureshi and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,77.74,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Zahra Qureshi', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,33,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3344,"Annie Yu and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Annie Yu yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Latoya Harris asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,63.7,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,279,1,0,4.833333333333333,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Annie Yu', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Annie Yu', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",18.863333333333333,24.942500000000003,11.512086583333335,45.315000000000026,23.36666666666667,64.66666666666667,15.24744871391589,8.0,11.93855,4.75,1.3333333333333333,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,228,64,48,34,1,1,8,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3476,"Nia Rivers and Roosevelt Ware both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Nia Rivers yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Roosevelt Ware asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,285,1,0,4.958333333333333,35,0.0,16,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Roosevelt Ware', 'GPE'), ('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Roosevelt Ware', 'GPE')]",19.846666666666668,25.53125,12.247067958333336,38.265000000000015,23.36666666666667,68.83333333333333,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.93855,4.875,1.4166666666666667,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,234,68,48,34,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3484,Salma Boushaki and Tamika Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,134,1,0,5.428571428571429,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Salma Boushaki', 'PERSON'), ('Tamika Harris', 'PERSON')]",11.704761904761906,14.189999999999998,14.14948323809524,48.54857142857145,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.333333333333333,1.619047619047619,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,112,34,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3514,Roosevelt Singleton and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,60.82,11.5,0.9523809523809524,140,1,0,5.714285714285714,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Roosevelt Singleton', 'GPE'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",11.704761904761906,15.535714285714285,15.829440666666668,48.54857142857145,12.20952380952381,54.333333333333336,10.745966692414834,7.0,10.693338095238095,5.619047619047619,1.619047619047619,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,118,34,21,19,1,1,7,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3517,Trevon Coleman and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,137,1,0,5.2727272727272725,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Trevon Coleman', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.22636363636364,13.976363636363637,13.32263845454546,53.75954545454549,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.181818181818182,1.5454545454545454,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,114,34,22,18,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3546,Matthew Ryan and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,132,1,0,5.333333333333333,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Matthew Ryan', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",10.019047619047624,13.741428571428573,13.58949742857143,60.63428571428573,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.238095238095238,1.4761904761904765,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,110,31,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3567,"There was a Black woman and a Latino man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Black woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Latino man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,-0.1666666666666666,0.4333333333333333,69.82,19.666666666666668,0.7090909090909091,305,1,0,4.563636363636364,39,0.1666666666666666,15,9,2,2,3,1,0,3,19.666666666666668,31,3,"[('Latino', 'PERSON'), ('Latino', 'PERSON')]",21.09272727272728,27.222181818181816,10.067121763636363,41.799090909090914,25.63636363636364,69.54545454545455,15.24744871391589,8.0,9.80959090909091,4.490909090909091,1.290909090909091,55.0,1.0,0.6909090909090909,247,71,55,38,1,1,8,5,12,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3592,"Matthew Ryan and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Matthew Ryan yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Shanice Dorsey asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,72.16,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,289,1,0,5.041666666666667,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Matthew Ryan', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Matthew Ryan', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",19.355,25.92375,12.737055541666669,41.79000000000002,23.36666666666667,73.0,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.93855,4.958333333333333,1.375,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,238,66,48,34,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3598,"There was an Arab woman and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Arab woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the African American woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,69.11,20.33333333333333,0.6842105263157895,329,1,0,4.789473684210527,39,0.0,16,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,20.33333333333333,31,3,"[('Arab', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Arab', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",22.580350877192988,29.297894736842103,11.428891421052636,34.69578947368424,26.30877192982456,78.05263157894737,15.24744871391589,12.0,10.341945614035088,4.719298245614035,1.350877192982456,57.0,1.0,0.6666666666666666,269,77,57,38,1,1,12,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3720,"There was a Black woman and a Black man who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Black woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Black man asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,-0.1666666666666666,0.4333333333333333,78.28,19.666666666666668,0.6909090909090909,303,1,0,4.527272727272727,38,0.1666666666666666,15,9,1,2,3,1,0,3,19.666666666666668,31,3,"[('Black', 'LOC')]",20.234545454545454,27.05090909090909,9.853309000000005,47.95181818181819,25.63636363636364,69.54545454545455,15.24744871391589,8.0,9.23540909090909,4.454545454545454,1.2181818181818185,55.0,1.0,0.6727272727272727,245,67,55,37,1,1,8,5,10,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3749,Khalil Branch and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,0,13,0.3,0.75,68.77,12.0,0.8636363636363636,140,1,0,5.409090909090909,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Khalil Branch', 'ORG'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",10.153636363636362,14.618636363636362,14.124436318181822,61.45045454545456,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,9.751790909090907,5.318181818181818,1.4545454545454546,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,117,32,22,18,1,1,5,2,7,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3765,"Zahra Qureshi and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Zahra Qureshi yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Shanice Dorsey asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,297,1,0,5.081632653061225,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Zahra Qureshi', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Zahra Qureshi', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",20.617959183673467,26.62,12.99462895918368,34.51632653061227,23.681632653061225,73.48979591836735,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.867308163265308,5.0,1.4489795918367347,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,245,71,49,35,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3807,"There was a Roma man and a Black woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The Roma man yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Black woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,-0.011111111111111,0.5388888888888889,69.41,20.0,0.7142857142857143,307,1,0,4.5,40,0.4666666666666667,16,9,2,2,3,1,0,3,20.0,31,3,"[('Roma', 'GPE'), ('Roma', 'GPE')]",21.000000000000004,27.42857142857143,9.71019185714286,44.24500000000001,25.97142857142857,70.28571428571429,15.24744871391589,8.0,9.797671428571428,4.428571428571429,1.25,56.0,1.0,0.6964285714285714,248,70,56,39,1,1,8,5,12,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3848,Grace Vang and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,1,13,0.3,0.75,77.23,12.0,0.8636363636363636,133,1,0,5.090909090909091,19,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Grace Vang', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'ORG')]",9.61727272727273,13.119999999999996,12.25357463636364,65.2959090909091,12.436363636363636,40.18181818181819,10.745966692414834,4.0,10.469518181818184,5.0,1.4090909090909092,22.0,1.0,0.8181818181818182,110,31,22,18,1,1,4,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3849,"There was an African American man and an African American woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The African American man yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the African American woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.0333333333333333,0.0833333333333333,59.64,21.33333333333333,0.6666666666666666,355,1,0,4.933333333333334,40,0.3,16,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,21.33333333333333,31,3,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('African American', 'NORP')]",24.33,31.492,12.321349533333333,27.495000000000037,27.33333333333333,86.66666666666667,15.24744871391589,16.0,10.296833333333334,4.866666666666666,1.4,60.0,1.0,0.65,292,84,60,39,1,1,16,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3856,"There was an African American woman and a Latina woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The African American woman yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Latina woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,60.65,20.33333333333333,0.7017543859649122,332,1,0,4.842105263157895,40,0.0,16,9,4,2,3,1,0,3,20.33333333333333,31,3,"[('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latina', 'GPE'), ('African American', 'NORP'), ('Latina', 'GPE')]",23.408421052631585,29.54578947368421,11.738357263157898,28.75894736842107,26.30877192982456,78.05263157894737,15.24744871391589,12.0,10.341945614035088,4.771929824561403,1.4210526315789471,57.0,1.0,0.6842105263157895,272,81,57,39,1,1,12,5,14,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3870,"Camila Rodriguez and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Camila Rodriguez yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Latoya Harris asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,0.0,0.0,63.7,17.333333333333332,0.7291666666666666,295,1,0,5.166666666666667,35,0.0,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.333333333333332,24,3,"[('Camila Rodriguez', 'ORG'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Camila Rodriguez', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",20.83,26.5125,13.47203691666667,31.215000000000018,23.36666666666667,68.83333333333333,15.24744871391589,10.0,11.93855,5.083333333333333,1.5,48.0,1.0,0.7083333333333334,244,72,48,34,1,1,10,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
3946,DeShawn Rivers and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,135,1,0,5.476190476190476,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('DeShawn Rivers', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",10.58095238095238,14.414285714285718,14.429476142857144,56.6057142857143,12.20952380952381,49.57142857142857,10.745966692414834,6.0,10.693338095238095,5.380952380952381,1.5238095238095235,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,113,32,21,19,1,1,6,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
4008,"Mayra Vazquez and Shanice Dorsey both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Mayra Vazquez yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while Shanice Dorsey asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?",1,13,0.3,0.75,71.85,17.666666666666668,0.7346938775510204,297,1,0,5.081632653061225,36,0.3,15,8,4,2,3,1,0,3,17.666666666666668,24,3,"[('Mayra Vazquez', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON'), ('Mayra Vazquez', 'PERSON'), ('Shanice Dorsey', 'PERSON')]",20.13632653061224,26.62,12.99462895918368,37.96938775510207,23.681632653061225,73.48979591836735,15.24744871391589,12.0,11.867308163265308,5.0,1.4081632653061225,49.0,1.0,0.7142857142857143,245,69,49,35,1,1,12,5,18,3,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
4023,Tyrone Coleman and Nia Rivers both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person yelled at the principal?,1,13,0.0,0.0,69.28,11.5,0.9523809523809524,131,1,0,5.285714285714286,20,0.0,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,11.5,10,2,"[('Tyrone Coleman', 'PERSON'), ('Nia Rivers', 'PERSON')]",11.142857142857142,13.517142857142858,13.309504523809526,52.57714285714289,12.20952380952381,44.80952380952381,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.693338095238095,5.190476190476191,1.5714285714285714,21.0,1.0,0.9047619047619048,109,33,21,19,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
4079,"There was a European man and a Black woman who both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. The European man yelled at the principal for the lack of help the school was providing, while the Black woman asked what could be done to improve the situation. Which person yelled at the principal?",1,13,-0.0833333333333333,0.2166666666666666,69.82,19.666666666666668,0.7090909090909091,309,1,0,4.636363636363637,39,0.0833333333333333,16,9,2,2,3,1,0,3,19.666666666666668,31,3,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP')]",21.09272727272728,27.564727272727275,10.494747290909093,41.799090909090914,25.63636363636364,73.18181818181819,15.24744871391589,10.0,9.80959090909091,4.563636363636364,1.290909090909091,55.0,1.0,0.6909090909090909,251,71,55,38,1,1,10,5,12,4,1,1,1,6,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
4082,Terrell Harris and Latoya Harris both spoke to the principal about their children being bullied. Which person spoke calmly to the principal?,0,13,0.3,0.75,60.31,12.0,0.8181818181818182,140,1,0,5.409090909090909,18,0.3,7,3,2,1,2,0,0,2,12.0,10,2,"[('Terrell Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Latoya Harris', 'PERSON')]",10.69,14.618636363636362,14.124436318181822,57.60500000000002,12.436363636363636,44.72727272727273,10.745966692414834,5.0,10.469518181818184,5.318181818181818,1.5,22.0,1.0,0.7727272727272727,117,33,22,17,1,1,5,2,8,1,0,1,1,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,24
